most of us
assume our mortgage will cost a lot and
take a long time to repay
but here's a secret it doesn't have to
your manulife bank mortgage
has a superpower prepayment privileges
here's how it works assume you owe three
hundred thousand dollars
each year you can make a one-time
payment of up to twenty percent
now most of us don't have that kind of
money lying around
but if you make an extra payment of just
five thousand dollars
you could save almost 8 500 and own your
home
eight months sooner you can also
increase your regular payment by up to
25 percent
if you pay your mortgage twice a month
and increase each payment by just fifty
dollars
you could save more than nineteen
thousand dollars and own your home
more than two years sooner wanna own
your home sooner
give us a call and let's get started